A chilling adventure!
Chill Out, Scooby-Doo! is a family, comedy,
animation film directed by Joe Sichta.
The gang's vacation to Paris takes a wrong turn when Scooby and Shaggy miss
their flight and end up on a skydiving expedition in the Himalayas.
To make matters worse, upon arrival they must outrun the Abominable Snowmonster.
Fred Jones / Scooby-Doo (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Shaggy Rogers (voice), played by Casey Kasem.
Daphne Blake (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Velma Dinkley (voice), played by Mindy Cohn.
Minga (voice), played by Kim Mai Guest.
Alphonse LaFleur (voice), played by René Auberjonois.
Chill Out, Scooby-Doo!
is a 2007 American animated comedy mystery film, and the eleventh in the
Scooby-Doo direct-to-video film series, produced by Warner Bros.
Animation, It was released to DVD on September 4, 2007.
The film is dedicated to Iwao Takamoto, a character designer for Hanna-Barbera who
died on January 8, 8 months before the film's home video release.
This was also the final Scooby-Doo!
movie that Joseph Barbera worked on before his death on December 18, 2006.
The film explores themes of paris, france, himalaya
mountain range, radio, vacation, traveling.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.